noktadomains.com 2019-01-16

# Privacy Policy | NoktaDomains

All users who log on to the Website are considered in scope of this Privacy Policy wheter or not they engage in any activity. Accordingly;

  * Personal information about members (name, nickname, e-mail address, mail address, phone information, credit card information, items bought etc.) is definately not shared with third parties excluding the circumstances undermentioned: 
    * Necessities arising from the legal rules such as Law, Decree Law, Regulation etc. which are in force and enacted by competent legal authority,
    * In case any information about the members are requested by competent administrative and legal authorities in accordance with an investigation made in due form,
    * In circumstances where it is necessary to disclose information in order to protect the member’s rights or security,
    * In cases where NOKTA finds it necessary for the fulfillment of the requirements of the “NOKTADOMAINS.COM” Membership Agreement and for the execution of these requirements and upon request of real or legal persons.
  * The users are solely in control of the content of the information submitted by themselves while becoming a member. NOKTA does not give permission to any third party to access to and change this information.
  * However, NOKTA reserves the right to analyse or make third parties analyse and share the obtained information about the members, other than the objectives and scope stated in the NOKTADOMAINS.COM Membership Agreement, in order to do direct marketing and/or to improve the services provided or to provide more exclusive and more effective services to its members. Within this scope; the information to be shared with third parties is limited with the statistical or demographic analysis such as members transactions within the Website, user profiles etc. and does not include member’s personal information.
  * When required, NOKTA has the right to ascertain and use the IP adresses of the members in order to determine and troubleshoot the problems about the system and the Website.
  * For safety reasons, NOKTA or it’s employees doesn’t keep any record about the credit card information of members, therefore they never ask or demand this kind of information from the members. The credit card information is transmitted to the related banks with the highest security standarts and bilateral connections. The credit card information is codified before transmission so the security of the information during the transmission is ensured.
  * In principle; all the transfer of information, transmisson, confirmation, order etc. is made via internet within the Website. However; for exceptional situations, a verbal or written confirmation of orders may be requested by the bank or our firm for the protection of our members. In that case, the bank or our firm has the right to reach the members from the contact information registered by the member.
  * NOKTA may give a link to other sites within the Website. NOKTA doesn’t have any liability regarding the privacy policies and contents of the linked sites.
  * Members hereby accept and declare that they are aware of the fact that NOKTA is using technical transmission files called “Cookie” with intent to avoid repeating commercials and password entry and to track activities within the Website.

**The privacy provisions stated herein is applied in order to provide a safer internet media according to NOKTA’s customer satisfaction principle and these provisions are an inseperable part and attachment of the Membership Agreement placed with our members.**

I have been informed by Nokta İnternet Teknolojileri Sanayi ve Ticaret A.Ş. (herein after referred as “Nokta Internet”) that, my personal data to be obtained by Nokta Internet as I purchase or rent domain services offered by Nokta Internet, can be processed and/or transferred in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Law ( Act. 6698) and the EU General Data Protection Regulation. 

In this respect, I hereby agree that my personal data including my name, surname, e-mail address, address, billing information and contact information can be processed verbally, in written or electronically in accordance with the purposes of,

  * \- Getting in contact during domain purchase or lease,
  * \- Sending invoices after domain purchase or lease,
  * \- Helping to verify accounts and transactions and ensuring security,

by automated or non-automated methods, web sites, social media, mobile applications, cookies and similar means.

Your personal data to be collected by Nokta İnternet Teknolojileri Sanayi ve Ticaret A.Ş. (herein after referred as “Nokta Internet”) as you purchase or rent domain services offered by Nokta Internet, are protected and processed in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act No. 6698 and the EU General Data Protection Regulation.

Personal Data and Personal Data Processing

Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.

Personal data processing means any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

Controller and Processor

Controller means the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data; where the purposes and means of such processing are determined by Personal Data Protection Act No. 6698.

Processor means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller.

Nokta İnternet Teknolojileri Sanayi ve Ticaret A.Ş. acts as controller on its own websites.

Personal Data Processing and Processing Purposes

As you become a member of our website; your personal data such as your name, surname, 

IP information, address information, e-mail address, traffic information, billing information, contact information and etc. can be collected and processed upon your explicit consent, orally, in written or electronically, with automated or non-automated methods, web sites, social media, mobile applications and similar means, in accordance with the terms of Personal Data Protection Act No. 6698 and its principles. 

Your personal data may be processed for the purposes listed below:

\- To be able to get in contact during domain purchase or leasing,

\- To be able to send invoices after domain purchase or lease,

\- To be able to help to verify accounts and transactions and to ensure security.

Individuals and Institutions to Transfer Personal Data and Purposes of Transfer

Your personal data collected and processed can not be transferred without your explicit consent, except in the case of exceptional provisions under Personal Data Protection Act No. 6698.

Your personal data, such as name, surname, address, etc., is not shared with third parties unless you have explicit consent.

Lawfulness and Method of Collecting Personal Data

Any personal data may be processed by Nokta Internet to be able to fulfill its legal obligations completely, upon explicit consent of the concerned persons mentioned in Articles 5 and 6 of the Personal Data Protection Act. 

Your personal data may be collected processed and transmitted orally, in written or electronically by means of automated, non-automated methods, cookies, web sites, social media, mobile applications and etc.

Rights of the Data Subjects Counted in Article 11 of the Personal Data Protection Act.

In accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act. No. 6698 you can apply to Nokta Internet for your rights;

a) To learn whether your personal data has been processed,

b) To request information about your processed personal data,

c) To learn the purpose of processing of your personal data and whether they are used appropriately,

d) To learn any third parties which are based domestic or abroad, that your personal data is transferred to,

e) To request correction of your personal data if it is imperfect or incorrectly processed,

f) To request your personal data to be deleted or destructed in accordance with the provisions of Article 7 of the Code,

g) To request any procedures done in accordance with your correction, erasure and destruction rights to be informed to any third party which your personal data has been transferred to,

h) To appeal against any adverse results of an analysis on your processed personal data by exclusively automated systems, 

i) To claim any losses arising due to illegal processing of your personal data to be compensated.

In accordance to Article 13 (1) of the Personal Data Protection Act. , unless any other method has been determined by the Personal Data Protection Board, you may convey your requests related to the rights mentioned above to Nokta Internet in written. In order to provide a proper and clear response to your requests, it is recommended that the content of your request to be clear, comprehensible and, significant by date.
